<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
<!-- tutorials' text -->
<korvaksub_submarine_tutorial>
    <h1>Interactible Items</h1>  
    The Sub contains a series of objects that look like decorations but are usable. 
    One example is the medical fabricator which looks like a red medical centrifuge but is actually interactible. 
    To see if an object is interactible or not, try hovering over it or even clicking it.  
    Most objects should be easy enough to distinguish from normal decorations.   

    <h1><b>Ballast</b></h1>  
    The ballast introduces two new movement systems, anti-ballast flora grenade and equipment and ballast flora detectors.  
        - tube system : The tube system allows moving from one end to the other of the ballast room by interacting with the pneumatic tube capsule.
                    do not worry about the number of capsule since they auto reset.  

        - grav lift : The gravitational lift or elevator allows moving swiftly up and down from the ballast room without the need of a ladder.
                    To go up just stand on it and let go /ragdoll. To go down just press the button to deactivate it and go down.

        - anti-ballast flora equipment : To combat ballast flora, new equipments are available to craft in the fabricator such as the antiballast grenade and canister to use with the sprayer.   

    <h1><b>Science Room</b></h1>  
    The science room has a containment unit that can store up to 4 alien artifacts and a set of automated greenhouses. 
    An automated greenhouse is just like a fabricator but for plants and requires seed and fertilizer.  

    <h1><b>Weapon Room</b></h1>  
    The weapon room or gun room introduces new weapons such as sets of artillery cannons, a missile launcher system and a microwave cannon.  

        - pneumatic transfer system : A set of two pneumatic tubes that are placed around both ends of the room to quickly transfer heavy objects by placing them inside.  

        - artillery cannons : Each artillery station controls a set of three artillery cannons. The cannons are aimed with the use of a valve and the cannons position is displayed through a monitor.  

        - valve : You can interact with valves and turn them by moving your mouse clockwise or counterclockwise in a circle.  

        - microwave cannon : The cannon is loaded through a system of small nuclear reactors, placed at the corners of the main reactor, which can be charged by using fuel rods. 
                             Do not that the reactor are interactible and quite small. 
                             To shoot the cannon you can interact with the monitor display near the reactor or just click the main reactor.  

    <h1><b>Torpedo System</b></h1>  
    The torpedo system is located near the right end of the the ballast room where you can load depth charges in the active torpedo.  
    The torpedo system can be controlled through the periscope in the Command Room and allows a certain amount of control over torpedos. 
    Do note that torpedos need to be armed before they can be launched. 
    Torpedos don't explode on contact but require to be remotely trigger from the torpedo periscope. Press one to launch and once again to detonate the active torpedo.  

</korvaksub_submarine_tutorial>
<korvaksub_drone_tutorial>
    Drones can be controlled from their respective stations. 
    Before we start, make sure that the drone hangar is open by changing its floor.  
    To Control a drone, you just have to sit in the control station, make sure it is turned on by flipping on the switch;
    and then control it through its small navigation UI.  
    Each drone can switch and cycle to a series of modes :  

    - drive mode 

    - turret mode 
    
    - special mode (not present in all drones)  

</korvaksub_drone_tutorial>
<!-- connections -->
<connection.turretaiminginx>position_in_[num]</connection.turretaiminginx>
<connection.turrettriggerinx>trigger_in_[num]</connection.turrettriggerinx>
<connection.turretaimingoutx>position_out_[num]</connection.turretaimingoutx>
<connection.turrettriggeroutx>trigger_out_[num]</connection.turrettriggeroutx>
<connection.setstatex>set_state_[num]</connection.setstatex>
<connection.togglestatex>toggle_state_[num]</connection.togglestatex>

</infotexts>